{
    "subject": "resource/Acacio_Gabriel_Viegas",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "Indian doctor",
    "human_readable": "Acacio Gabriel Viegas is described as an Indian doctor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9164671301841736,
            "question": "What kind of doctor is Acacio Gabriel Viegas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9106862545013428,
            "question": "Is Acacio Gabriel Viegas a medical professional?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8013685941696167,
            "question": "What is Acacio Gabriel Viegas's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7349226474761963,
            "question": "What is Acacio Gabriel Viegas known for in the medical field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6745983958244324,
            "question": "What country does Acacio Gabriel Viegas represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6019983291625977,
            "question": "Where is Acacio Gabriel Viegas from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5636530518531799,
            "question": "Where might one find more information about Acacio Gabriel Viegas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5039050579071045,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Acacio Gabriel Viegas's education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46045470237731934,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Acacio Gabriel Viegas's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3892325460910797,
            "question": "Does Acacio Gabriel Viegas have any notable accomplishments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Acacio Gabriel Viegas is described as an Indian doctor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3544_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Acacio Gabriel Viegas's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3544_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Acacio Gabriel Viegas's education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3544_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might one find more information about Acacio Gabriel Viegas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3544_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3544_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3544_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3544_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3544_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3544_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3544_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3544_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3544_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3544_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3544_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about Acacio Gabriel Viegas, including his profession (medical practitioner), nationality (Indian), and contributions to public health. The documents also mention that he was credited with the discovery of the outbreak of bubonic plague in Bombay, India in 1896, and that he inoculated no less than 18,000 persons personally with a new serum prepared by Dr. Hafkine.\n\nThese details support the triple statement that Acacio Gabriel Viegas is described as an Indian doctor."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Acacio Gabriel Viegas is described as an Indian doctor.\" For example, several documents describe him as a medical practitioner and doctor, including his role in discovering the outbreak of bubonic plague and his work during the epidemic."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}